<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="mobius.simplify.feature"
      label="Simplify Feature"
      version="1.5.5"
      provider-name="EU MOBIUS IST-15905 Project">

   <description url="http://kind.ucd.ie/products/opensource/ESCJava2/">
      This feature wraps the latest release of the Simplify automatic theorem prover.
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.hpl.hp.com/downloads/crl/jtk/">
      Copyright (c) 2002 Hewlett-Packard Company.
Portions (c) 2004-2007 Joe Kiniry, Radboud University Nijmegen,
and University College Dublin.
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.hpl.hp.com/downloads/crl/jtk/agreement.html">
      Software License Agreement

This software, and other information, is protected by copyright laws and international treaties.  Hewlett-Packard Company, and its subsidiary Hewlett-Packard Development Company, L.P., (collectively “HP”) reserves all rights except those expressly granted below.

© Hewlett-Packard Development Company, LP

HP does not warrant the accuracy or completeness of the software and other information.  This software and other information may have errors or other defects.  Any use made of, or reliance on, such information is entirely at user’s own risk.

By downloading any software or other information you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this license agreement.

You may download and use personally the software for non-commercial purposes free of charge or further obligation.  Your may not, directly or indirectly, distribute the software for a fee, incorporate this software into any product offered for sale, or use the software to provide a service or a product for which a fee is charged.

You may download, modify and redistribute the software to individuals for personal, non-commercial purposes free of charge provided that such individuals agree to only use the modified software according to the terms of this agreement. 

The software and other information is furnished “as is” without any expressed or implied warranty of any kind.  All implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a purpose are disclaimed.  HP shall not be liable for any direct, indirect, special, incidental or consequential damages arising out of any use of the software and other information.

For inquiries please contact: Hewlett-Packard Company.
   </license>

   <url>
      <update url="http://kind.ucd.ie/products/opensource/Simplify/simplify-eclipse/updates/"/>
      <discovery label="The original Simplify technical report." url="http://www.hpl.hp.com/techreports/2003/HPL-2003-148.pdf"/>
      <discovery label="The ESC/Java2 release website.  The latest Simplify releases are always included with ESC/Java2." url="http://kind.ucd.ie/products/opensource/ESCJava2/"/>
      <discovery label="The Java Programming Toolkit Source Release website at Hewlett-Packard." url="http://www.hpl.hp.com/downloads/crl/jtk/"/>
   </url>

   <plugin
         id="mobius.simplify.plugin"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"/>

</feature>
